Prakashbhai Koli

Computer Science

Experienced IT Specialist with a good background in designing and developing. 1+ years of industry experience. Excellent problem solving skills and ability to perform well in a team. Seeking to help company, as well as grow and develop my own skills.

koliprakashbhai555@gmail.com

Pune, India

prakashbhai555.github.io/pkportfolio/

+91- 79723-94788

05 May, 1995

in linkedin.com/in/prakashbhai-koli-99711819b

WORK EXPERIENCE

jr. Software Developer (Intern) Hands in Technology

01/2020 - 07/2020 Kandivali, Mumbai

handsintechnology.com

- As Intern was working on Magento2 PHP Framework for updating, solve some config. file bugs, as well as manually Testing some Live Projects on Android, iOS, and web App.

Associate Software Engineer Vistaar Digital Media Pvt. Ltd.

07/2021 - 03/2022 Boriwali, Mumbai

www.vistaardigital.com

- As Software Engineer experienced on developing web application and work on Emailers, Edetailing, Git, SQL, JS, Drupal, WordPress, WIX

EDUCATION

Master of Computer Application

R.C Patel Institute Of Management Research And Development, Shirpur

08/2017 - 04/2020 NMU, Jalgaon 64.00 %

- Computer Science

Bachelor of Computer Science

S.P.D.M College, Shirpur

07/2014 - 01/2017 NMU, Jalgaon 62.00 %

- Computer Science

HSC

New High School, Taloda

07/2011 - 05/2012 Nashik Board 51.33

- Science Stream

SSC

K.P.Patil School, Bhaler

07/2009 - 05/2010 Nashik Board 74.60

- Marathi Medium

SKILLS

Energetic

TECHNICAL SKILL

SQL, PL/SQL, C++

HTML, CSS, PHP

Emailers, Edetailing, Git

Magento2, WordPress, WIX, Figma

COLLEGE PROJECTS

One Stop NRI Advisory. (Smart Mobile Application)

In the project Admin can provide the packages and subservices for user to order as per there requirements . The need of this project is Windows platform, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, PHP, MySQL, JS, etc.

CERTIFICATES

Basics of SQL Database Management System (SCALER)

Python Training 🛂

Introduction to WordPress 🗹

Front end Development - HTML

MY WORK/OTHERS LINKS

Dribbble (UI/UX Designing Portfolio)

Online Shopping (Made with Google Site for shopping)

LANGUAGES

English Hindi

Professional Working Proficiency Full Professional Proficiency

Marathi

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

INTERESTS/HOBBIES

Puzzle Solving

Photography

Travelling